i'm going to teach you how to hula hoop
around your waist for beginners
to get started take your hoop grab it
with both your hands and you're going to
place your hoop on your back like this
the next step is you're going to step
one foot in front of you
then you want to make sure that you are
standing up straight
the next step is to take your hoop and
you're going to wind it up
and give it a nice big spin around your
body
and you're really going to focus on that
rocking back and forth
motion make sure to avoid rocking from
your shoulders like this
because if you do that there's a chance
the hoop may just fall right down
really focus on isolating your shoulders
and doing that rocking back and forth
motion while really
flexing those ab muscles the hulu size
that you use
is super important for the beginners out
there i do recommend that you use
a larger hoop size usually larger hoops
are
easier to use when you first start out